Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Motion Pictures
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Videorecordings documenting Yale University, 1966-2008; Accession 2009-A-156
  - 3084: Yale Bumps tape #2: b-roll commencement, student life news clippings, Yale Club greetings, undated; 1 (Box 48)
  - 3085: Yale Bumps tape #3, b-roll: Tercentennial, speakers, sciene labs, undated; 1 (Box 924)
  - 3092: Select Reel campus, undated; 1 (Box 52)
  - 3098: Worcester Square, undated; 1 (Box 58)
  - 3110: Yale European Buisness Profile, undated; 1 (Box 68)
  - 3111: Light Blue Movie Clip 1, undated; 1 (Box 69)
  - 3112: Light Blue Movie Clip 2, undated; 1 (Box 70)
  - 3113: Light Blue Movie Clip 3, undated; 1 (Box 71)
  - 3114: Light Blue Movie Clip 4, undated; 1 (Box 72)
  - 3116: Yale Happy Birthday, undated; 1 (Box 74)
  - 3118: Devane Clips and Birthday greetings, undated; 1 (Box 76)
  - 3119: Yale Club Colorado Birthday greetings, undated; 1 (Box 77)
  - 3123: Yale Club of Vermount, undated; 1 (Box 81)
  - 3124: Yale Club of Los Angeles, undated; 1 (Box 82)
  - 3126: Campus Yale, undated; 1 (Box 84)
  - 3242: Benjamin Bolger, Dateline, NBC, undated; 1 (Box 871)
  - 3275: New Haven Initiative Press Conference, undated; 1 (Box 185)
  - 3305: Am I Blue, undated; 1 (Box 213)
  - 3312: Free Speech and Advertising - Who Draws the Line?, undated; 1 (Box 220)
  - 3314: :60 TV Spot, undated; 1 (Box 222)
  - 3316: A Time for Learning, undated; 1 (Box 224)
  - 3329: Yale University - The Table at Berkeley, undated; 1 (Box 237)
  - 3332: Yale Rebuilds: The Restoration of Calhoun College, undated; 1 (Box 240)
  - 3336: A Time for Learning - Yale Office of Admissions, undated; 1 (Box 244)
  - 3340: Yale Athletics Welcomes the World, undated; 1 (Box 248)
  - 3351: Keep the Promise: Lean About Lead, undated; 1 (Box 259)
  - Reinventing Yale, 1998 February 26; 1 (Box 279)
    This video is a duplicate of 3369: Reinventing Yale, 1998 February 26
  - 3386: Secret Society, undated; 1 (Box 288)
  - 3387: Mega Science and Public Policy, Bromley lecture, undated; 1 (Box 289)
  - 3389: Mega Science and Public Policy, Applequist lecture, undated; 1 (Box 874)
  - 3399: Norfolk Chamber Music Festival, undated; 1 (Box 300)
  - 3400: Yale Great Teachers Series - Psychology, undated; 1 (Box 301)
  - 3401: Mega Science and Public Policy lecture on high performance computing science, undated; 1 (Box 875)
  - 3407: Scientia, undated; 1 (Box 305)
  - 3409: Freshman Crime Prevention and Habitat for Humanity, undated; 1 (Box 307)
  - 3413: Biotechnology, undated; 1 (Box 311)
  - 3414: Three Degrees of Freedom - Bugler Juggling Robot, undated; 1 (Box 312)
  - 3417: Congressional Outlook #109, television deregulation, undated; 1 (Box 933)
  - 3418: Levin Inauguration / Conference on Yale Housing Program, undated; 1 (Box 934)
  - 3419: Congressional Outlook, Bob Gilbert, St. Pete Times, undated; 1 (Box 935)
  - 3420: Inflation: The Economy in Crisis, NBC Television, undated; 1 (Box 936)
  - 3423: Cocaine Addiction Discovery, undated; 1 (Box 314)
  - 3424: New Therapy to Treat Epilepsy, undated; 1 (Box 315)
  - 3429: Town Gown Panel, undated; 1 (Box 320)
  - 3431: Inquiring Mind: Sciences at Yale, undated; 1 (Box 322)
  - 3470: The Spirit of Yale: A commitement to excellence, undated; 1 (Box 334)
  - 3474: Athletics Promo video, undated; 1 (Box 335)
  - 3492: European Business Profile: Yale, undated; 1 (Box 347)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 347U)
  - 3522: International Travel Review, undated; 1 (Box 373)
  - 3523: Yale Promo tape followed by DeVane Lecture, undated; 1 (Box 374)
  - 3524: Yale Promo tape, development, undated; 1 (Box 375)
  - 3531: Yale Promo tape, student life, undated; 1 (Box 900)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 900U)
  - 3525: Campus b-roll, various buildings, some crane shots, undated; 1 (Box 376)
  - 3528: Campus b-roll, students in lecture hall, no audio [PAL format], undated; 1 (Box 378)
  - 3529: Campus b-roll, students reading and relaxing, undated; 1 (Box 131)
  - 3530: Yale Compilation B-Roll Part 2, undated; 1 (Box 379)
  - 3532: Video Introduction to Yale College, undated; 1 (Box 324)
  - 3536: Coverage of Jovin murder, undated; 1 (Box 132)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 132U)
  - 3541: Convergence and other rituals on the NH Green, undated; 1 (Box 383)
  - 3544: Telecome City, MA: The Power of Collaboration, undated; 1 (Box 386)
  - 3546: Everybody's Business: Next Generation of Environmental Policy, undated; 1 (Box 388)
  - 3547: National Institute of Health for Policy Research, undated; 1 (Box 389)
  - 3549: We Dared to Win: 25 years of Womens Ivy League Championship, undated (Box 390)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 390U)
  - 3552: Hill Central Park video plus Assorted shots from Kellert's class, undated; 1 (Box 393)
  - 3554: Coeducation at Yale 1970 and antiwar protests, undated; 1 (Box 395)
  - 3570: Employee Orientation, undated; 1 (Box 411)
  - 3571: International Travel Review, undated; 1 (Box 412)
  - 3576: John Pepper Speech, undated; 1 (Box 417)
  - 3650: Policy and Perspectives, undated; 1 (Box 427)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 427U)
  - 3655: CBS Evening News - Racial Bias Test, undated; 1 (Box 432)
  - 3660: Cutting Edge - Tele Medicine, undated; 1 (Box 436)
  - 3663: Jovin Murder, undated; 1 (Box 439)
  - 3667: Is This You? Health and Biosciences, undated; 1 (Box 443)
  - 3668: A Question of Safety, undated; 1 (Box 444)
  - 3672: Yale University, undated; 1 (Box 447)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 447U)
  - 3679: Yale Compilation Footage, undated; 1 (Box 453)
  - 3681: Wishnow: Eye of the Beholder, undated; 1 (Box 455)
  - 3689: Yale University and New Haven, Town and Gown Relations, undated; 1 (Box 462)
  - 3690: Yale and New Haven: A New Social Contract, undated; 1 (Box 463)
  - 3691: A Greater New Haven: "Let It Shine", undated; 1 (Box 464)
  - 3764: Yale University Democratic Vistas, undated; 1 (Box 470)
  - 3765: BIG NIGHT, undated; 1 (Box 471)
  - 3766: Chicago's Front Page, undated; 1 (Box 472)
  - 3769: NYSE: A Portrait, undated; 1 (Box 475)
  - 3776: Portrait of an Ital-American Community, undated; 1 (Box 479)
  - 3779: Portrait of FDR, undated; 1 (Box 482)
  - 3794: Clips, AV studio, undated; 1 (Box 494)
  - 3798: Jennifer Beals, undated; 1 (Box 498)
  - 3869: Gilmore Girls, Lorelei's First Day at Chilton, undated; 1 (Box 538)
  - 3878: Looping Master, Opening Yale 300/300 Years, undated; 1 (Box 545)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 545U)
  - 3882: Yale a Place for Poetry, undated; 1 (Box 547)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 547U)
  - 3892: Shots of the Medical School, b-roll, undated; 1 (Box 963)
  - 3895: The Eternal Road, Frank Productions, undated; 1 (Box 966)
  - 3896: The Years @ Yale 1952-1953, undated; 1 (Box 549)
  - 3902: One Story, Many Voices, Yale University Women's Organization, undated; 1 (Box 554)
  - 3913: National College Review, undated; 1 (Box 563)
  - 3916: Creating Global University, undated; 1 (Box 565)
  - 3920: Levin Intelligence Commission, undated; 1 (Box 569)
  - 3921: A Place of Dreams, undated; 1 (Box 570)
  - 3926: Roots in Wales, undated; 1 (Box 575)
  - 3932: Today Show, undated; 1 (Box 581)
  - 3961: Gaddis Smith, discussion of Yale Presidents, undated; 1 (Box 598)
  - 3963: Yale TV Spots: Peabody, Visitor Center, Yale Art Gallery, undated; 1 (Box 600)
  - 3966: Dinotopia Dig Contest, Channel 8 Promo, undated; 1 (Box 603)
  - 3967: Yale Visitor Center, Art Gallery, Events, WTNH ad spots, undated; 1 (Box 604)
  - 3980: Yale Youth, Channel 8, undated; 1 (Box 616)
  - 3990: Weish In Hollywood, undated; 1 (Box 625)
  - 3991: Yale, by Bjorn-Christoph Bugl, undated; 1 (Box 626)
  - 3992: AET Image Engineering, Lasers, undated; 1 (Box 627)
  - 3993: Beat the Odds Graduation Stories, Oprah, undated; 1 (Box 628)
  - 3994: Bright College Years, undated; 1 (Box 629)
  - 4001: Cybersurgery: Dominican Republic, Discovery Health Channel, undated; 1 (Box 635)
  - 4003: OCR Biotech, undated; 1 (Box 637)
  - 4009: Block Taping of NBC 75, WVIT and WTIC, undated; 1 (Box 643)
  - 4010: Block Taping of News Channel 8, undated; 1 (Box 644)
  - 4011: Block Taping of News, WFSB and CNN, undated; 1 (Box 645)
  - 4012: Block Taping of News, WVIT and WTIC, undated; 1 (Box 606)
  - 4013: Block Taping of News, Julia Roberts tapes movie in New Haven, undated; 1 (Box 611)
  - 4014: Block Taping of News, Parking in New Haven around campus, undated; 1 (Box 918)
  - 4020: ConCom Inc. Demo Reel, undated; 1 (Box 648)
  - 4022: Science Park, NBC 30 Biotechnology News, undated; 1 (Box 649)
  - 4023: Block Taping of News, NBC 30, undated; 1 (Box 917)
  - 4024: Gilmore Girls, undated; 1 (Box 650)
  - 4025: HBO Block Taping, Curb Your Enthusiam and Sex in the City, undated; 1 (Box 651)
  - 4057: To be a man, undated; 1 (Box 683)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 683U)
  - 4059: Yale B Roll (Presidential Sites), JE, Mory's, Law School, Skull and Bones, Bush home, undated; 1 (Box 685)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 685U)
  - 4060: Russian T.V., undated; 1 (Box 686)
  - 4064: Autism: Paying The Price, undated; 1 (Box 690)
  - 4090: Drama School Stage Blue CNN News Clip, undated; 1 (Box 713)
  - 4098: Yale at 300, undated; 1 (Box 714)
  - 4104: Yale 300: Making a Difference, undated; 1 (Box 711)
  - 4105: A Message from the President, Yale University Birthday, undated; 1 (Box 727)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 727U)
  - 4108: Doonesbury - Gary Trudeau, undated; 1 (Box 733)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 733U)
  - 4122: Renewal and Renaissance, undated; 1 (Box 740)
  - 4163: Vietnam 30 Years On, undated; 1 (Box 712)
  - 4282: The Big Picture Guide to College, Brown University, undated; 1 (Box 155)
  - 4292: Through My Eyes, Office for Victims of Crimes, undated; 1 (Box 341)
  - 4298: Levin and Chanda, undated; 1 (Box 451)
  - 4303: Dr. Suchitra Krishnan - Yale Medical School, undated; 1 (Box 524)
  - 4311: Dr. Liane Philpotts - Yale School of Medicine, undated; 1 (Box 578)
  - 4323: Boston: Highly Informed Voters, undated; 1 (Box 729)
  - 4324: Boston: College Donors, undated; 1 (Box 723)
  - 4325: Iowa: Parents of Undergrads, undated; 1 (Box 724)
  - 4326: Iowa: Male Voters, undated; 1 (Box 726)
  - 4327: San Diego: Parents of High School Students, undated; 1 (Box 738)
  - 4328: San Diego: Women Voters, undated; 1 (Box 750)
  - 4134: George W. Bush Profile, undated; 1 (Box 751)
  - 4135: William Sloane Coffin Conversation I, undated; 1 (Box 752)
  - 4136: William Sloane Coffin Conversation II, undated; 1 (Box 753)
  - 4161: Vietnam 30 Years On, undated; 1 (Box 776A)
  - 4162: Vietnam 30 Years On, undated; 1 (Box 776B)
  - 4166: Clinton At Yale, Yale Student Soundbite on "Dead Animals on the Wall", undated; 1 (Box 779)
  - 4167: Yale Engineering PSA, undated; 1 (Box 780)
  - 4168: Levin Baccalaureate, undated; 1 (Box 781)
  - 4169: Get To Know New Haven, WTNH, undated; 1 (Box 782)
  - 4170: Science at Yale, undated; 1 (Box 783)
  - 4172: Making the Right Moves: Blacks in Corporate America, undated; 1 (Box 785)
  - 4173: New Haven Update I, AYA, undated; 1 (Box 786)
  - 4174: New Haven Update II, AYA, undated; 1 (Box 787)
  - 4175: New Haven Update III, AYA, undated; 1 (Box 788)
  - 4176: Bass Family Donations, undated; 1 (Box 789)
  - 4177: Yale's Undegraduate Colleges, AYA, undated; 1 (Box 790)
  - 4178: Yale College Residential Colleges I, undated; 1 (Box 791)
  - 4179: Yale College Residential Colleges II, undated; 1 (Box 792)
  - 4180: Yale College Residential Colleges III, undated; 1 (Box 793)
  - 4181: Yale College Residential Colleges, AYA, undated; 1 (Box 794)
  - 4218: Building Our Future Together, Yale and New Haven, undated; 1 (Box 819)
  - 4222: Corporation Room Interviews 1, undated; 1 (Box 823)
  - 4223: Corporation Room Interviews 2, undated; 1 (Box 824)
  - 4224: Swenson Interviews, undated; 1 (Box 825)
  - 4226: Community Leadership Award to Richard C. Levin, undated; 1 (Box 827)
  - 4244: Contributing to a Strong New Haven, Yale University", undated; 1 (Box 837)
  - 4249: Arabic TV Interview with Richard Levin", undated; 1 (Box 842)
  - 4250: Yale University: A Global Institution, undated; 1 (Box 843)
  - 4251: Yale University Campus B-Roll, undated; 1 (Box 844)
  - 4273: Fueling the Future, Princeton Plasma Physics Lab", undated; 1 (Box 858)
  - 4275: China Revealed, Discovery, undated; 1 (Box 860)
  - 4278: Pearl and Herman's 5th Anniversary, Ram Video Productions, undated; 1 (Box 863)
  - 4281: CDCP in the Media, undated; 1 (Box 866)